# LIN TUNGYAO(TANYA)

Taipei, Taiwan lucktanya33@gmail.com

#### INTRODUCTION

I have interest in web development while I were a project manager for a website which maintain medical online service. In April 2021, I joined Lidemy Bootcamp to learn web developting both front-end and back-end for six months.

I make a TDEE colories calculator to by vanilla Javascript. Also I use morden framework React and express.js to develop a stock-searching website StockMeow which is deplyed on Heroku.

- Skills
   HTML, CSS Javascript
   React/Node.js/
   express.js
   Git/npm/webpack
- Certificates TOEIC 920 IELTS 6.5
- Education
   Master of Public Affair,
   National Changhua
   University of Education
   2018~2020

### **PROJECTS**

#### TDEE calculator Vanila Javascript, CSS, HTML



This fitness website lets you enter age, weight, height, and activity level, to know how many calories you need to consume per day. You can also put your custormized goal for cutting fat or gaining weight.

## **Demo | Github Repo**

#### StockMeow React, Node.js, Heroku



This website is for searching Taiwan stock information and offers a discussion platform for the enrolled member.

StockMeow will update stock prices every day through TWSE API. This website is built with the modern framework React

and express.js. Front-end and Back-end are deployed on Github and Heroku.

Demo | Github Repo

# **EXPERIENCES**

# <u>Lidemy Bootcamp</u>, student – April, 2021

- Learning web development in both front-end and back-end
- Weekly assignments would be code reviewed by tutors who work in the software industry
- Through online Bootcamp, enriching my ability in joining communities and debugging

## NutureFit, project manager - August, 2020~Now

- Build TDEE calculator to reduce dietitians calculating time
- Write the spec of the website and communicate with engineers
- Through keyword planning platform, GA, search console, PageSpeed to maintain website traffic

# NCUE Center for Institutional Research, assistant – Jan, 2020~July 2020

- Web crawling the result college entrance exam for analyzing the possibility of competing institution
- Re-design code structure to reduce crawling time by python